FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

in/raul-lc/

contact@ralo.dev

+52 951 408 4018

Oaxaca, México

ralo.dev

SUMMARY

I'm a Full Stack Developer with more than 1 year of experience in web development. I'm adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Passionate programmer with drive to learn and master new technologies.

LANGUAGES

Spanish **Native** English C1 (TOEFL Certified)

SKILLS & TOOLS

Backend

- Java
- TypeScript
- Spring Boot
- Nestis
- MySQL, PostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- Supabase, Firebase
- Strapi

Frontend

- HTML5, CSS, JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Tailwind
- JQuery
- Vue.is
- React

WORKING EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Technologial Institute of Oaxaca JAN 2024 - PRESENT I'm contributing to the development of an institutional system using Nestjs and TypeScript

FULL STACK DEVELOPER INTERNSHIP

Technologial Institute of Oaxaca MAY 2022 - JUL 2023 I was responsible for the development of a web application for the management of the institution's HR

- Optimized report generation times by 90%
- Developed a fully functional HRMS using **Spring Boot** and Vue.js
- Succesfully deployed and mantained the HRMS hosted at https://itoaxaca.tech

EDUCATION

department.

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SYSTEMS **ENGINEERING**

2018 - 2023

National Technological Institute of Mexico